[
  {
    "option c": "Regression testing",
    "option d": "Sanity testing",
    "answer": "a",
    "Question": "Which testing is done by developer?",
    "option a": "Unit testing",
    "option b": "Integration testing"
  },
  {
    "option c": "Closed-box testing",
    "option d": "Security testing",
    "answer": "d",
    "Question": "Which is non functional testing?",
    "option a": "Unit testing",
    "option b": "Integration testing"
  },
  {
    "option c": "Endurance testing",
    "option d": "All of the above",
    "answer": "d",
    "Question": "Which is performance testing ?",
    "option a": "Spike testing",
    "option b": "Scalability testing"
  },
  {
    "option c": "9",
    "option d": "10",
    "answer": "a",
    "Question": "How many principles of testing are there?",
    "option a": "7",
    "option b": "8"
  },
  {
    "option c": "4",
    "option d": "5",
    "answer": "b",
    "Question": "How many types of prority of bug/defect are there?",
    "option a": "2",
    "option b": "3"
  },
  {
    "option c": "Critical",
    "option d": "Major",
    "answer": "c",
    "Question": "A defect indicates complete shutdown of the process. Which types of severity of bug it falls under?",
    "option a": "Low",
    "option b": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "option c": "Exploratory testing",
    "option d": "Monkey testing",
    "answer": "b",
    "Question": "Test is conducted at one or more customer sites by the end-user of the software. Which type of testing is this?",
    "option a": "Alpha testing",
    "option b": "Beta testing"
  },
  {
    "option c": "System testing",
    "option d": "Acceptance testing",
    "answer": "c",
    "Question": "A type of testing where tester evaluates the whole system against the specified requirements",
    "option a": "Integration testing",
    "option b": "Unit testing"
  },
  {
    "option c": "Penetration testing",
    "option d": "Volume testing",
    "answer": "d",
    "Question": "Flood testing is another name of -",
    "option a": "Endurance testing",
    "option b": "Scalability testing"
  },
  {
    "option c": "Load testing",
    "option d": "Stress testing",
    "answer": "a",
    "Question": "Soak testing is another name of -",
    "option a": "Endurance testing",
    "option b": "Volume testing"
  },
  {
    "option c": "5",
    "option d": "6",
    "answer": "b",
    "Question": "How many levels of testing ?",
    "option a": "3",
    "option b": "4"
  },
  {
    "option c": "4",
    "option d": "5",
    "answer": "a",
    "Question": "How many types of testing based on the test execution?",
    "option a": "2",
    "option b": "3"
  },
  {
    "option c": "2",
    "option d": "4",
    "answer": "c",
    "Question": "How many types of testing based on the testing objectives?",
    "option a": "3",
    "option b": "5"
  },
  {
    "option c": "3",
    "option d": "2",
    "answer": "d",
    "Question": "How many types of acceptance testing?",
    "option a": "4",
    "option b": "5"
  },
  {
    "option c": "Adhoc testing",
    "option d": "Localization testing",
    "answer": "c",
    "Question": "An unstructured way of testing that is performed without any formal documentation",
    "option a": "Volume testing",
    "option b": "Sanity testing"
  }
]